TALK HARD. STEAL THE AIR.
Pump Up the Volume is a music, drama film directed by Allan Moyle.
Mark Hunter, a lonely high school student, uses his shortwave radio to moonlight as the popular pirate DJ "Hard Harry." When his
show gets blamed for a teen committing suicide, the students clash with high school faculty and the authorities.
Mark Hunter, played by Christian Slater.
Nora Diniro, played by Samantha Mathis.
Loretta Creswood, played by Annie Ross.
Brian Hunter, played by Scott Paulin.
Marla Hunter, played by Mimi Kennedy.
Murdock, played by Andy Romano.
Pump Up the Volume is a 1990 coming-of-age teen drama
film written and directed by Allan Moyle.
The film stars Christian Slater, Scott Paulin,
Ellen Greene, and Samantha Mathis.
The film explores themes of rebellion, high school, suicide, hero, authority.
The tone is emotional.